JUAN JOSE TELLEZ TOBON FullStack Developer



Portfolio



in Linked-in



juanjose250699@gmail.com



WhatsApp



Colombia

About me

Industrial Engineer and Full Stack Developer, specialized in project management with a professional level of English. Throughout my education, I had the opportunity to engage in tasks related to internal audits, occupational health and safety, and web programming, spanning various levels of complexity. I am committed to continuous learning and delivering value with my acquired skills.

Soft Skills

Adaptable to new situations | Proficient in problem-solving | Team Work | Communication Skills

Tech Skills

JavaScript|HTML|CSS|ReactJS|Express|MySQL|EJS|NodeJS|Sequelize|APIS|Git|Github|WireFrimes|JSON| Express-session | CRUD process | Cookie-parser

Languages

Spanish - Native Language English - Professional

Professional Experience

Freelance (Full Stack Developer)

January 2023 - Present

Grinding Coffee

Grinding Coffee is an e commerce that uses JavaScript as main tool, along with Express, Node.js, JSON, EJS, and CSS. The project is continuously updated, with a final version expected soon.

Mercado Liebre

Mercado Liebre is a project that serves as a practice exercise, modeled after the Mercado Libre website, allowing me to test my skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript (Backend), Express, and Node.js."

Expresify

This is a future project that I'm working on with a friend, aiming to utilize all the tools we've learned, including JavaScript, Express, MySQL, EJS and NodeJs. We're hopeful that it will become a reality soon as an own company.

JappWorkout

It's a project I've developed entirely using ReactJS. It's responsive for all kind of devices and designed to provide a solution for athletes who want an effective workout routine. It not only counts their sets but also measures the time between them, providing a strict track of the exercises they perform.

Industrial Engineer

January 2019 - November 2023

Developing an information system using Visual Basic to organize data received by the mayor's office. Development of financial and accounting activities, as well as accountability, for the Department of Information Technology and Communications.

Provide support in Internal Audits, link with the Department of Economic Development, and reception and consolidation of observations made by the Mayor's Office regarding Delegated Contracting.

Education

Full stack Developer

September 2023 - April 2024

Project management specialist

March 2021 - April 2022

Industrial Engineer January 2017 - March 2021